SUNISH SUDHARSANAN

IT MANAGER BCA - Computer Application +918848246674





www.linkedin.com/in/sunish- in sudharsanan-b0b1ab121

Profile

IT Manager with over 7 years of professional experience with expertise in installation of network and computer system, maintenance of IT network, servers, and security systems, repair and up gradation of operating system including hardware and software.

Skills

- Hardware Desktop, Laptop, Server, Networking, CCTV, Printer, Scanner, Access control, Access points, Switches, Router, Firewall, EPBX, NAS.
- OS Windows XP, 7, 8, 10, Server2012 R2, Linux.
- Software pfSense, CMS, MS Office, O365

Experience

19 NOV 2019 - PRESENT

IT MANAGER / ProEmTech Infosystems Pvt Ltd / INDIA

Responsibilities

- Installation & maintenance of desktop, laptop, Server, CCTV, Firewall, Router, Access point, Printer,
- Installation & maintenance of EPBX and Telephone.
- ❖ Installation & maintenance of storage device (NAS).
- O365 Administration.
- Installation & maintenance of Networking & ISP.
- Installation & maintenance of IoT devices (UrgenZ, PresenZ, Anges, KiKo ProEmTech products).
- Work as a team member in developing new IoT devices.
- Handling IT vendors.
- Taking care of all IT assets.

08 AUG 2018 - 30 AUG 2019

CCTV Engineer / QWERTY SOLUTIONS / UAE

Projects - CCTV installation in Fujairah Mall, Century Mall, Ajman University, Al Hilal Bank

Responsibilities

- Planning & Designing of CCTV System according to Fujairah police rules.
- Taking approval for the CCTV drawing from Fujairah police.
- Coordinating CCTV installation with subcontractors.

❖ Installation & maintenance of Point To Point system for Fujairah police.

08 JUNE 2016 - 07 JUNE 2018

CCTV Technician / Overlook Security Systems LLC / UAE

Projects – CCTV installation in Rosewood Hotel, Stepping Stone Nursery, Structured caballing in Sharjah Airport Responsibilities

- Installation & configuration of CCTV.
- Coordinating with sub contractors.
- Giving technical support for remote viewing.
- Coordinating with SIRA for CCTV approvals.

08 APRIL 2014 - 29 APRIL 2016

System Engineer / ProEmTech Infosystems Pvt Ltd / INDIA

Responsibilities

- ❖ Installation & configuration of computer hardware & software.
- Planning and designing of system networks.
- Giving technical support for clients.

Education

MAY 2009

Graduation/SAS SNDP Yogam College Konni, Pathanamthitta, Kerala

Bachelor of Computer Application First class – 67.78%

MARCH 2006

HSE / Govt Higher Secondary School, Kalanjoor, Kerala

Distinction – 76.67%

MARCH 2004

SSLC / St. Stephen's Higher Secondary School, Pathanapuram, Kerala

Distinction - 81.50%

Reference

Pleased to provide on request.